# Nicholas Mamberger

I aim to make a career in full stack web development. My past job experiences so far have been as a courier driver, server, Lifeguard, swim coach, tiling apprentice, stocker, deli associate, and talent acquisition scout.

Richfield, MN 55423 nhmamberger@gmail.com +1 952 454 3394

More importantly, I have been learning skills involving react, Node.js, JavaScript, and so much more web development skills in becoming a full stack web developer.

I will have a link to my own coding portfolio soon...

My recent work has been in driving/courier for Amazon and have had some training and experience with UPS, BUT i do have a certification through SoloLearn, an online training website, for Java and i have been working on getting my certification through Python and C++ as well. I have been working for a long time and have a variety of experience in the workplace but what I would say it comes down to, to describe in short summary would be: my willingness to work hard is exceptional, willing to learn and take on new challenges, and that I strive to do it all to try and provide for my wife and future family of our own.

https://www.sololearn.com/Certificate/1068-25797103/pdf/

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

# Work Experience

#### **Courier Driver**

CROWN DELIVERY AND LOGISTICS - Eagan, MN August 2018 to Present

Delivering packages from 50 pounds or less. Lots of experience training new people and helping rescue other drivers. Passed DOT CERTIFICATION for Drivers. On average I have been working for 50 hours a week. Well past the average 40 hours per week most drivers just work but i have also worked in excess of 65 hours in a work week and I am usually willing to work overtime. This job has required a lot of driving through all seasons in around a lot of the twin cities area and i have delivered in so many cities that it can be a long list to name off.

#### **Produce Stocker**

Costco Wholesale - Burnsville, MN November 2017 to August 2018

Stocking during the hours of 5am to 10am, sometimes 1:30pm. Able to work in a fast paced environment and perform individual tasks where needed. Started out from working seasonal with no guarantee of a job unless you can make the team by displaying the job skills they want at a competitive level. I was able to get the job where some did not.

### **Tiling Apprentice**

Steve's tiling - Burnsville, MN March 2014 to August 2018

Steve's Tiling Company, Burnsville, MN

Also note that I would drive a truck for this job and help deliver supplies to the job site such as 80 pound bags of concrete and other items and tools for the job.

#### **Sandwich Artist**

Panera Bread - Burnsville, MN February 2016 to October 2017

Employee of the month was an accomplishment I made while i was working here.

#### **Deli Associate**

Walmart - Burnsville, MN August 2016 to November 2016

Able to serve customers at low to high demand under circumstances regarding using a fryer, slicer, telethon, oven for rotisseries, and various kitchen utensils. During any of my active cooking or cleaning duties I was required to help the customer and provide them with helpful assistance.

# Lifeguard

YMCA - West Saint Paul, MN May 2015 to October 2016

#### Responsibilities

I have to provide emergency oxygen, CPR, AED use, and First Aid when needed to patrons of the pool and when needed in the facility. I provide water chemical testing too and general care such as maintenance to the pool like basic cleaning tasks when needed too.

## Accomplishments

I provided a positive hard working attitude there along with good service skills to the people to provide them a safe and fun time at the pool.

#### Skills Used

I demonstrated that i am sharp and focused when it comes to spotting those in need of care around the pool. I provided support to kids when they were afraid and i got the chance to save 2 kids before in a life endangered environment.

### Server

The Rivers - Burnsville, MN May 2013 to October 2015

#### Responsibilities

I served residents who have retired and i provided them with great hospitality while serving them appetizers, main meals such as breakfast, brunch, lunch, and dinner. I was able to serve them with high courtesy and respect letting them know that i really do care about each resident there and i worked well with my coworkers too. I became a team lead server and i have experience in leadership and chef assisting too.

# Accomplishments:

The residents there that i served all got excellent service from me. My boss and fellow coworkers saw that i was willing to be diligent in providing good work ethic. I was able to be flexible to provide emergency or well needed help on short notice to come in and work for almost anyone. I was able to get employee of the month due to my hard work and dedication to providing the residents care to their needs with a great attitude and service.

#### Skills Used

Like i said i am flexible, hard working, and i am a positive person in my field. I was able to demonstrate good leadership and solid work ethic to new coworkers and train in people who just started working there as their first job and got them into a good working habit while showing them how it is always good to serve positively and cater to their needs.

# Education

# **Communications Degee in Interpersonal Communications**

Bethany Lutheran College - Mankato, MN January 2016 to June 2016

Burnsville Senior High School - Burnsville, MN 2014

### Skills

- Microsoft Office, Google docs, google applications, powerpoint, google apps, intermediate level typing. Learning coding in python and more subjects through data camp and trying to complete certificates there as well as some projects in coding recently over the past month. (1 year)
- Driver
- fast learner
- Drivina
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Office
- Courier
- Swimming
- Lifeguard
- Pool Maintenance
- Delivery Driver Experience

### Links

https://www.sololearn.com/Certificate/1068-25797103/pdf/

### Certifications and Licenses

### DOT

# **DOT Delivery Driver Certification**

# **First Aid Certification**

### **CPR Certification**

# **AED Certification**

# **Lifeguard Training**

# Additional Information

#### Skills

- \* Flexible and self directed in my work place as far as completing tasks without having to be told.
- \* Diligent and arrives on time to work.
- \* Can team lead with my fellow coworkers and coordinate them to serve well and close up when we finish work.
- \* Responsible in fulfilling orders such as when serving and providing my customer with their meal and great satisfaction.
- \* Self-Directed
- \* I can drive and I have my own ride.
- \* I have proper certification to work as a lifeguard and I have CPR and First Aid training
- \* I can type well and complete forms.